SAGAR WASULE

.NET CORE, MVC, Web API & ANGULAR (FULL STACK DEVELOPER)

Mobile +91-9766917505

Email <u>sagarwasule@gmail.com</u>

Skype Sagarwasule

LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/i

n/sagarwasule

Website www.sagarwasule.in

I am a technology professional with more than 7.2 years' experience. I am technically a .NET developer with a wellearned reputation for developing .net web application using MVC Framework, C#, JQuery, Angular, Web API, .Net Core

<u>Microsoft Certified Solutions</u> <u>Associate (MCSA) - Web Applications</u>



CERTIFICATIONS

Programming in HTML5 with JavaScript and CSS3 Dec 2012

Microsoft License 70-480

Developing ASP.NET MVC Web ApplicationsJan 2017

Microsoft License 70-486

Scrum Fundamental Certified

Scrum Study July 2017

AWARDS

Hero of moment Dec 2017 Decos Software Development Pvt Ltd

Team Impact Award Jun 2017 Decos Software Development Pvt Ltd

Star of the Month

Tata Consultancy Services Nov 2013

WORK EXPERIENCE

System Analyst May 2018 – Present

Ivy Comptech (GVC Holding PLC)
Location: Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Senior Software Developer Jan 2016 – Apr 2018

Decos Software Development Pvt Ltd Location: Pune, Maharashtra, India.

Senior Software Engineer Jan 2015 - Jan 2016

Cybage Software

Location: Pune, Maharashtra, India.

System Engineer Dec2011 - Dec 2014

Tata Consultancy Services

Location: Pune, Maharashtra, India.

EDUCATION

B.E in Electronics and Telecommunication

66.18 % Jun 2007 - Jun 2011

Yeshwantrao Chavan College of Engineering

Nagpur University Nagpur, Maharashtra, India

H.S.C in Electronics

82.00 % Jun 2006 -May 2007

Nutan Bharat Junior College Maharashtra State Board

s.s.c

74.80 % Jun 2004 -May 2005 St. Xavier's High School Maharashtra State Board

SKILLS

PRIMARY SKILLS	Microsoft TechnologiesNET(C# & ASP.NET), MVC Framework, Web API, HTML, CSS, .Net Core	
SECONDARY SKILLS	WCF, Swagger-UI, Redis, Apache Kafka, Elastic Search	
DATABASE	SQL Server, MySQL	
SCRIPTING LANG.	AngularJs 1.x, Angular 5+, Typescript, JQuery, JavaScript	
DOMAIN SKILLS	Banking and Finance, Product Development	
TOOLS USED	Visual Studio, GIT, Stash, Web Deploy, SQL Management Studio, TFS, Visual Studio Code, Kafka Tool	
OPERATING SYSTEM	Windows 10, Windows 8.1, Windows 7	
LINGUISTIC SKILLS	English, Hindi and Marathi	

www.sagarwasule.in **Mobile**: +91-9766917505 **Email**: sagarwasule@gmail.com

IVY COMPTECH (GVC HOLDING PLC)

Project	Scoreboard Client	
Period	Sept 2018 – Present	
Designation	System Analyst	Role: Tech Lead - Web Developer
Client	GVC Group	Team Size: 6
Responsibilities	1. Designing, developing and im-	plementing the solutions.
	2. Performed deployments on De	ev, Test environment.
	3. Assigning task to team memb	ers and perform scrum ceremonies
Project	1. This project involves developing	ng a client application which will be used by
Description	Scoreboard operators who car	n update the latest scores which in turn will
	be passed to Active Scoreboar	ds on various websites.
	2. Project follows Agile Scrum m	ethodology.
	3. This application is used by cli	ents across the globe.
Skill	C#, .Net Core, .Net Core Web API, An	gular 6, Kafka, Redis, SQL, Elastic Search
Tools Used	Visual Studio 2017, Visual Studio Co	ode, SQL server

Project	Sports Label Building
Period	May 2018 - Sept 2018
Designation	System Analyst Role : Tech Lead - Web Developer
Client	GVC Group Team Size : 7
Responsibilities	1. Designing, developing and implementing the solutions.
	2. Performed deployments on Dev, Test environment.
	3. Assigning task to team members and perform scrum ceremonies
Project	1. This project was to develop sport labels for various clients in gambling
Description	industry for GVC group
	2. Involved in partial migration of code from AngularJs to Angular 5
	application.
	3. Project follows Agile Scrum methodology.
	4. This application is used by clients across the globe for Sports betting.
Skill	C#, .Net MVC, .Net Web API, AngularJs, Angular 5
Tools Used	Visual Studio 2017, Visual Studio Code

DECOS SOFTWARE PVT. LTD.

Project	Cartracker	
Period	January 2016 – April 2018	
Designation	Senior Software Developer Role : Web Developer	
Client	Decos Mobile Solutions By Team Size : 7	
Responsibilities	1. Gathering and analyzing the requirements, understanding the complexity	
	and providing work estimates	
	2. Designing, developing and implementing the solutions.	
	3. Performed deployments on Dev, Test and Production environment.	
	4. Providing technical guidance to team members.	
Project	1. Cartracker is an IOT product which can be integrated with vehicles and	
Description	get real time vehicle position and complete analysis of the trips recorded.	
	2. This project consists of hardware, backend and web client application.	
	3. Project follows Agile Scrum methodology.	

www.sagarwasule.in **Mobile**: +91-9766917505 **Email**: sagarwasule@gmail.com

	4. This application is used by client for various analyses of trips primarily
	used in Europe.
Skill	C#, .Net MVC, .Net Web API, AngularJs, MySQL, Redis
Tools Used	Visual Studio 2015, HeidiSQL

CYBAGE SOFTWARE

Project	RMS eBubble	
Period	January 2015 – January 2016	
Designation	Senior Software Engineer Role : Mo	odule
	Lead	
Client	RISARC Consulting, LLC Team	Size :
	15	
Responsibilities	1. Gathering and analyzing the requirements, understanding the com-	plexity
	and providing work estimates	
	2. Designing, developing and implementing the solutions.	
	3. Performed deployments on Dev, Test and Production environment.	
	4. Providing technical guidance to team members and reviewing task.	
Project	1. This project involves maintenance and enhancement of RMSeBubble	
Description	Application.	
	2. This involved enhancement and maintaining the current applicatio	n
	according to the business needs.	
	3. This application is used by client for various analyses in Healthcar	re
	domain by to share patient's documents in secured way.	
Skill	C#, .Net MVC, AngularJs, SQL	
Tools Used	Visual Studio 2012, SQL Server 2008	

TATA CONSULTANCY SERVICES

Project	FA Tools
Period	December 2012 – December 2014
Designation	System Engineer Role : Developer
Client	Morgan Stanley Team Size : 5
Responsibilities	1. Gathering and analyzing the requirements, understanding the complexity
	and providing work estimates
	2. Designing, developing and implementing the solutions.
	3. Performed deployments on Dev, Test and Production environment.
	4. Supporting the QA, UAT and performance testing of the application.
	5. Providing support to the FA Tools applications in Production
	6. Developed documentation for API in swagger
Project	1. This project involves maintenance and enhancement of in all 6
Description	applications used by financial advisors internal to Morgan Stanley for
	various financial analyses.
	2. This involved enhancement and maintaining the current application
	according to the business needs and as per release schedule.
Skill	.Net MVC, WCF Restful Service, JQuery, ExtJS, AngularJS, and JavaScript.
Tools Used	Microsoft Visual Studio 2008/2010/2012

Project	.Net Migration (.Net 1.1 to .Net 4.0 Migration)	
Period	September 2012 – December 2012	
Designation	Assistant System Engineer	Role : Developer
Client	Morgan Stanley	Team Size: 8
Responsibilities	1. Gathering and analyzing the requirements, under	rstanding the complexity
	and providing work estimates	

	2. Migration of .Net 1.1 components to .Net 4.0 framework
	3. Peer reviewing the tasks of the team to ensure quality
Project	1. Client possessed various applications that were in .Net 1.1
Description	2. Since Microsoft would soon be withdrawing the support for .Net 1.1, it was
	necessary to migrate these applications to the .Net 4.0 framework
	developed web applications.
	3. This project included migration of applications to .Net 4.0 framework
Skill	.Net MVC, Asp .Net C#, and JavaScript.
Tools Used	Microsoft Visual Studio 2010

Project	End user Technology
Period	April 2012 – August 2012
Designation	Assistant System Engineer Role : Developer
Client	Morgan Stanley Team Size : 4
Responsibilities	 Analyzing the requirements, understanding the complexity and providing work estimates Developing required features
	3. Peer reviewing the tasks of the team to ensure quality
Project Description	1. Client had various legacy applications in VB which are used by Financial Advisors (FAs).
	 Since Microsoft would soon be withdrawing the support for VB6, it is necessary to migrate the users from legacy applications to the newly developed web applications. This project included developing applications in Asp.Net 4.0 framework
Skill	Asp .Net C#, SQL and JavaScript.
Tools Used	Microsoft Visual Studio 2010, SQL Server 2008

PERSONAL DETAILS

Name	Sagar Girish Wasule
Email Id	sagarwasule@gmail.com
Contact No.	+91-808797505
	+91-9766917505
Date Of Birth	05-10-1989
Current Location	Hyderabad, India
Preferred Location	Pune, India

I hereby declare that above mentioned information are true in the best of my knowledge and belief.

SAGAR WASULE